freesharewaredepot.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy FreeSharewareDepot

This privacy statement was written in accordance with the provisions of United Stated Laws, regarding individual protection about collecting and free circulation of personal data.

FreeSharewareDepot Network has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy over the internet. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: FreeSharewareDepot.com is operated by FreeSharewareDepot Network, located in Scottsdale, Arizona United States.

During the administration process of the website, FreeSharewareDepot needs to take over some personal information, in order to improve the website usage. FreeSharewareDepot respects and grants confidentiality for personal data collected over from its users at several different points on the website:

  * We are the sole owners of the information gathered within the FreeSharewareDepot website.
  * We shall not sell or rent this information to others in any way.
  * We shall not share this information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

The clauses of this policy are valuable for all kinds of information gathered from FreeSharewareDepot users. Additional clauses, if any, will be added if necessary for special services that we may offer in the future. This privacy policy informs you about the type of personal data that we may collect from you, the way we can use it, the way we understand to protect it, who has access to it and how the possible mistakes can be corrected.

Web Site Security  
FreeSharewareDepot is a trusted and secure web-site as is detailed in this Web Security Certificate:

Information that we collect  
FreeSharewareDepot may collect information from its users in three different ways:

  * Directly from the user.
  * Information from traffic references of hosting servers.
  * Information from cookies.

 **Information provided directly by the user:** when you subscribe to a service provided by FreeSharewareDepot, we may ask you about your name and e-mail address. For example, when you fill the contact form, you need to enter your name and valid e-mail address.

 **Information from traffic references:** when you visit a website, you unveil certain information about you, such as your IP address, time of visit, place from which you accessed our website. FreeSharewareDepot, like other operators, stores this information.

 **Information from cookies:** FreeSharewareDepot allows other companies, called third-party ad networks or payment registration services such as Google Adsense [Google Adsense Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/ "Google Adsense Privacy Policy") and RegNow Software Registration Services [MyCommerce Privacy Policy](http://corporate.digitalriver.com/store/digriv/Corp/sectionName.company/subSectionName.corpPolicies/page.corpPolicies#privacy "RegNow Privacy Policy"), to serve advertisements or software purchase within the FreeSharewareDepot site. These third-party companies use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the FreeSharewareDepot site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

FreeSharewareDepot does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks FreeSharewareDepot to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, men ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the FreeSharewareDepot Sites, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You need to acknowledge that, whenever you disclose information in public areas on the website, such as message boards comments, that information becomes public and can easily be tracked and used by unauthorized persons. Although FreeSharewareDepot does its best in order to protect your personal data, we cannot entirely grant you its safety. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. You should also know that you are the only one responsible for keeping the secret of your passwords, usernames etc.

How and when we use the information:

FreeSharewareDepot uses the information collected from you for several purposes, depending on the type of data collected:

  * information provided directly by the user: this information is used only in order to personalize the services that we offer you and to check your identity.
  * information from traffic references: this type of info helps us identify the parts of our site of most interest for you. FreeSharewareDepot also collects the IP addresses of its users, in order to safely manage our computer system.

How we protect information collected from you

We show great interest in confidentiality. FreeSharewareDepot does not offer your personal data to third parties without your prior express consent. Any statistics that we may offer to our partners or to advertisement networks does not include any personal identifying information about any individual user.

Unfortunately, no data transmission by means of internet can be 100% sure. As a consequence, despite our efforts to protect your personal data, FreeSharewareDepot cannot guarantee the safety of your information. All this kind of transmission whatsoever is made on your own risk.

Still, we can grant you that we carry out all our efforts to ensure safety for our systems, according to the security standards imposed by Romanian legislation. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff checks server access daily to ensure the above holds true.

Unsolicited communication

FreeSharewareDepot will not use your e-mail address in order to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail. It is your choice whether you decide to receive or not newsletters from us. You can always choose to unsubscribe from our newsletter services.

Who has access to the information collected from you

As a rule, FreeSharewareDepot will never unveil any sort of personally identifiable information about any of its users, without their prior express consent. On the other hand, FreeSharewareDepot may unveil this kind of data when expressly permitted by law or when this measure is necessary in order to protect FreeSharewareDepot rights and interests.

As a conclusion, when you access FreeSharewareDepot website and are asked to offer information about you, only FreeSharewareDepot will have access to them. However, you acknowledge that our site contains links to some partner sites. FreeSharewareDepot is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. We do not share this information with third parties.

We may use an outside ad company (only Google AdSense) to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

Advertisements served by Google, as a third party vendor, use DART cookies. These cookies are used to serve ads based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

How we can correct errors contained by data collected from you

If you're a Software Author and send us your products to be included on our site, we shall send you a confirmation e-mail in which we give you the details of the newly created account. The confirmation message will be sent at the e-mail address that you provided. We strongly advise you to keep this confirmation mail secret, because it contains information that can be useful when you encounter problems in accessing our services.

Children's Guidelines

This site gives children under the age of 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum.

Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact FreeSharewareDepot. For any suggestions and comments regarding FreeSharewareDepot or our Privacy Policy, please contact us at.

This Privacy Policy is guided by the United Stated legislation and has been updated today, November 1, 2014.
